export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Land Registration Act of 1903 now PD 1529, Nov 6 1902",
    options: ["a. EO 208", "b. RA 6652", "c. Act 496", "d. Act 2259"],
    correct: "c. Act 496",
  },
  {
    question: "Public Land Act Nov 7, 1936",
    options: ["a. Commonwealth Act 141", "b. Act 411", "c. Act 400", "d. Commonwealth Act 411"],
    correct: "a. Commonwealth Act 141",
  },
  {
    question: "Property Registration Decree June 11, 1978",
    options: ["a. PD 1216", "b. RA 7279", "c. PD 1529", "d. PD 957"],
    correct: "c. PD 1529",
  },
  {
    question: "Cadastral act, 11 Feb 1913",
    options: ["a. PD 1216", "b. PD 1185", "c. Act 1903", "d. Act 2259"],
    correct: "d. Act 2259",
  },
  {
    question: "Indigenous People Rights Act",
    options: ["a. RA 8736", "b. RA 6657", "c. RA 8371", "d. RA 7160"],
    correct: "c. RA 8371",
  },
  {
    question: "Subdivision and Condominium Buyers Protective Decree, 12 July 1976",
    options: ["a. PD 1529", "b. PD 1517", "c. PD 1216", "d. PD 957"],
    correct: "d. PD 957",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Authorizing DHSUD to enforce differentiated standards and technical requirements for economic and socialized housing projects. 25 March 1982",
    options: ["a. BP 220", "b. PD 957", "c. PD 1158", "d. RA 9904"],
    correct: "a. BP 220",
  },
  {
    question: "Family Code of PH, 3 Aug 1998",
    options: ["a. BP 220", "b. PD 2146", "c. RA 11201", "d. EO 209"],
    correct: "d. EO 209",
  },
  {
    question: "Local Government Code of PH 1991",
    options: ["a. RA 9646", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 7160", "d. RA 6657"],
    correct: "c. RA 7160",
  },
  {
    question: "Real Estate Service Act of PH. June 29, 2009",
    options: ["a. RA 9646", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 7160", "d. RA 6657"],
    correct: "a. RA 9646",
  },
  {
    question: "Urban Development and Housing Act. March 24, 1992",
    options: ["a. RA 9646", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 7279", "d. RA 6657"],
    correct: "c. RA 7279",
  },
  {
    question: "Condominium Act. June 18, 1966",
    options: ["a. RA 9646", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 7160", "d. RA 4726"],
    correct: "d. RA 4726",
  },
  {
    question: "Real Estate Investment Trust Act (REIT). Dec 16 2009",
    options: ["a. RA 9646", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 7160", "d. RA 9856"],
    correct: "d. RA 9856",
  },
  {
    question: "Realty Investment Buyer's Protection Act or MACEDA Law. Aug 26, 1972",
    options: ["a. RA 9856", "b. RA 6552", "c. RA 7160", "d. RA 6657"],
    correct: "b. RA 6552",
  },
  {
    question: "Home Guaranty Corporation Act of 2000",
    options: ["a. RA 9646", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 7160", "d. RA 6657"],
    correct: "b. RA 8763",
  },
  {
    question: "Open Space (in Residential Subdivision) of 1977",
    options: ["a. PD 1216", "b. PD 1529", "c. PD 957", "d. PD 1517"],
    correct: "a. PD 1216",
  },
  {
    question: "Urban Land Reform Act. June 11, 1978",
    options: ["a. PD 1216", "b. PD 1529", "c. PD 957", "d. PD 1517"],
    correct: "d. PD 1517",
  },
  {
    question: "Comprehensive Agrarian Reform Law (CARL). June 10, 1988",
    options: ["a. RA 9646", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 7160", "d. RA 6657"],
    correct: "d. RA 6657",
  },
  {
    question: "Comprehensive Agrarian Reform Program (CARP extension). Aug 7, 2009 and valid until June 30, 2014",
    options: ["a. RA 9646", "b. RA 9700", "c. RA 7160", "d. RA 6657"],
    correct: "b. RA 9700",
  },
  {
    question: "Revised National Building Code of Ph. Feb 18, 1977",
    options: ["a. PD 1216", "b. PD 1529", "c. PD 957", "d. PD 1096"],
    correct: "d. PD 1096",
  },
  {
    question: "Fire Code of PH. Aug 26, 1977",
    options: ["a. PD 1216", "b. PD 1185", "c. PD 957", "d. PD 1096"],
    correct: "b. PD 1185",
  },
  {
    question: "Environmental Impact Statement (EIS) System. June 11, 1978",
    options: ["a. PD 1216", "b. PD 1185", "c. PD 1586", "d. PD 1096"],
    correct: "c. PD 1586",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Identifies Environmentally Critical Projects (ECPs) and areas (ECAs) under the Environmental Impact Statement (EIS) System",
    options: ["a. PD 2146", "b. PD 1185", "c. PD 1586", "d. PD 1096"],
    correct: "a. PD 2146",
  },
  {
    question: "Amends Condominium Act to streamline governance and protect unit owners rights. Feb 23, 1995",
    options: ["a. RA 9646", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 7899", "d. RA 6657"],
    correct: "c. RA 7899",
  },
  {
    question: "Ecology Solid Waste Management Act of 2000",
    options: ["a. RA 9646", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 7160", "d. RA 9003"],
    correct: "d. RA 9003",
  },
  {
    question: "Department of Human Settlements and Urban Development Act (DHSUD). Feb 14, 2019",
    options: ["a. RA 7899", "b. RA 11201", "c. RA 7160", "d. RA 11953"],
    correct: "b. RA 11201",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Consolidated and codified all Internal Revenue laws in PH into a unified framework. Enacted on 1976. Amended by PD 1994 and EO 273 VAT 1987",
    options: ["a. PD 2146", "b. PD 1185", "c. PD 1586", "d. PD 1158"],
    correct: "d. PD 1158",
  },
  {
    question:
      "National Internal Revenue Code (NIRC) – Dec 11, 1997. Consolidated and amended PD 1158, PD 1994, and EO273.",
    options: ["a. RA 9646", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 8424", "d. RA 6657"],
    correct: "c. RA 8424",
  },
  {
    question: "Tax Reform for Acceleration and Inclusion (TRAIN) Act. Dec 19, 2017",
    options: ["a. RA 10963", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 7160", "d. RA 11953"],
    correct: "a. RA 10963",
  },
  {
    question: "Corporate Recovery and Tax Incentives for Enterprise (CREATE) Act. March 26, 2021",
    options: ["a. RA 10963", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 11534", "d. RA 11953"],
    correct: "c. RA 11534",
  },
  {
    question: "New Agrarian Emancipation Act. July 7, 2023",
    options: ["a. RA 10963", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 11534", "d. RA 11953"],
    correct: "d. RA 11953",
  },
  {
    question: "Magna Carta for Homeowners Association. October 13, 2009",
    options: ["a. RA 9646", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 7160", "d. RA 9904"],
    correct: "d. RA 9904",
  },
  {
    question: "National Home Mortgage Finance Corporation (NHMFC). Dec 21, 1977",
    options: ["a. PD 2146", "b. PD 1185", "c. PD 1267", "d. PD 1158"],
    correct: "c. PD 1267",
  },
  {
    question: "National Housing Authority. July 31, 1975",
    options: ["a. PD 757", "b. PD 957", "c. PD 1267", "d. PD 1158"],
    correct: "a. PD 757",
  },
  {
    question: "Social Housing Finance Corporation (SHFC) a subsidiary of NHMFC",
    options: ["a. Act 1039", "b. PD 757", "c. EO 272", "d. PD 1267"],
    correct: "c. EO 272",
  },
  {
    question: "National Building Code of PH Aug 26, 1972 (later revised PD 1096 in 1977)",
    options: ["a. PD 1096", "b. RA 8763", "c. PD 757", "d. RA 6541"],
    correct: "d. RA 6541",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Foreign Investments Act of 1991 (amended RA 8179 and RA 11647). Former natural born Filipinos can acquire land for business up to 5,000sqm urban areas or 3 hectares in rural areas",
    options: ["a. RA 7160", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 7042", "d. RA 6541"],
    correct: "c. RA 7042",
  },
  {
    question: "Anti Red Tape Act of 2007 (amended by RA 11032 – Ease of Doing Business Act of 2018)",
    options: ["a. RA 9485", "b. RA 8763", "c. RA 7042", "d. RA 11032"],
    correct: "a. RA 9485",
  },
  {
    question: "PD 957",
    options: [
      "a. National Housing Authority",
      "b. Tax Reform for Acceleration and Inclusion",
      "c. Urban Development and Housing Act",
      "d. Subdivision and Condominium Buyers Protective Decree",
    ],
    correct: "d. Subdivision and Condominium Buyers Protective Decree",
  },
  {
    question: "RA 9646",
    options: [
      "a. National Housing Authority",
      "b. Real Estate Service Act of PH",
      "c. Promote economic and socialized housing developments, through private sector initiatives",
      "d. Corporate Recovery and Tax Incentives for Enterprise (CREATE) Act",
    ],
    correct: "b. Real Estate Service Act of PH",
  },
  {
    question: "BP 220",
    options: [
      "a. Promote economic and socialized housing developments, through private sector initiatives",
      "b. Anti Red Tape Act",
      "c. Subdivision and Condominium Buyers Protective Decree",
      "d. National Housing Authority",
    ],
    correct: "a. Promote economic and socialized housing developments, through private sector initiatives",
  },
  {
    question: "EO 209",
    options: [
      "a. Fire Code of PH",
      "b. Local Government Code",
      "c. National Housing Authority",
      "d. Family Code of PH",
    ],
    correct: "d. Family Code of PH",
  },
  {
    question: "RA 7279",
    options: [
      "a. Real Estate Service Act of PH",
      "b. Urban Development and Housing Act",
      "c. Corporate Recovery and Tax Incentives for Enterprise (CREATE) Act",
      "d. Foreign Investments Act",
    ],
    correct: "b. Urban Development and Housing Act",
  },
  {
    question: "RA 4726",
    options: [
      "a. Urban Development and Housing Act",
      "b. Anti Red Tape Act",
      "c. Condominium Act",
      "d. New Agrarian Emancipation Act",
    ],
    correct: "c. Condominium Act",
  },
  {
    question: "RA 9856",
    options: [
      "a. Condominium Act",
      "b. Urban Development and Housing Act",
      "c. Real Estate Investment Trust Act (REIT)",
      "d. Foreign Investments Act",
    ],
    correct: "c. Real Estate Investment Trust Act (REIT)",
  },
  {
    question: "RA 6552",
    options: ["a. Real Estate Service Act", "b. Anti Red Tape Act", "c. Condominium Act", "d. MACEDA Law"],
    correct: "d. MACEDA Law",
  },
  {
    question: "RA 8763",
    options: [
      "a. Home Guaranty Corporation Act",
      "b. Condominium Act",
      "c. Urban Development and Housing Act",
      "d. Real Estate Service Act",
    ],
    correct: "a. Home Guaranty Corporation Act",
  },
  {
    question: "PD 1216",
    options: [
      "a. National Building Code",
      "b. National Housing Authority",
      "c. Tax Reform for Acceleration and Inclusion",
      "d. Open Space (in Residential Subdivision)",
    ],
    correct: "d. Open Space (in Residential Subdivision)",
  },
  {
    question: "RA 9700",
    options: [
      "a. Comprehensive Agrarian Reform Program (CARP)",
      "b. Urban Development and Housing Act",
      "c. Home Guaranty Corporation Act",
      "d. Condominium Act",
    ],
    correct: "a. Comprehensive Agrarian Reform Program (CARP)",
  },
  {
    question: "RA 7899",
    options: [
      "a. Urban Development and Housing Act",
      "b. Home Guaranty Corporation Act",
      "c. Amends Condominium Act",
      "d. Condominium Act",
    ],
    correct: "c. Amends Condominium Act",
  },
  {
    question: "RA 11201",
    options: [
      "a. Magna Carta for Homeowners Association",
      "b. National Home Mortgage Finance Corporation",
      "c. National Housing Authority",
      "d. Department of Human Settlements and Urban Development Act (DHSUD)",
    ],
    correct: "d. Department of Human Settlements and Urban Development Act (DHSUD)",
  },
  {
    question: "RA 9904",
    options: [
      "a. Department of Human Settlements and Urban Development Act (DHSUD)",
      "b. Magna Carta for Homeowners Association",
      "c. Housing and Land Use Regulatory Board (HLURB)",
      "d. National Home Mortgage Finance Corporation (NHMFC)",
    ],
    correct: "b. Magna Carta for Homeowners Association",
  },
  {
    question: "PD 757",
    options: [
      "a. National Housing Authority",
      "b. National Home Mortgage Finance Corporation (NHMFC)",
      "c. Open Space",
      "d. Tax Reform for Acceleration and Inclusion",
    ],
    correct: "a. National Housing Authority",
  },
  {
    question: "EO 272",
    options: [
      "a. Department of Human Settlements and Urban Development Act (DHSUD)",
      "b. National Home Mortgage Finance Corporation (NHMFC)",
      "c. National Housing Authority",
      "d. Social Housing Finance Corporation (SHFC)",
    ],
    correct: "d. Social Housing Finance Corporation (SHFC)",
  },
  {
    question: "PD 1096",
    options: [
      "a. National Building Code of Ph",
      "b. National Housing Authority",
      "c. National Home Mortgage Finance Corporation (NHMFC)",
      "d. Social Housing Finance Corporation (SHFC)",
    ],
    correct: "a. National Building Code of Ph",
  },
]
